I might have seen a lot of candy for the first time.
Cute!
My friend's color
Home run.
Ah!
Home run!
Hello, everyone!
I'm Hina Kawada of Hinakazoka46.
Today is the third installment of the Hina Walk.
The first one is at Takao-san.
The second one is cycling.
The second one was a cycling tour in Takao.
But this time, we're finally going to do something a little more relaxed.
What is it?
We're going to a sushi restaurant!
Yay!
The reason why we are going to a dagashiya is because...
I love dagashi.
When I was in elementary school...
I used to go to a dagashiya every day after school with 100 yen in my pocket.
I love dagashiya so much that I used to go there every day after school with 100 yen in my pocket.
This is the first time I'm sharing this information with you.
So this time I visited a nice dagashiya and
I'd like to get a lot of dagashi!
Today's item...
How much is it?
Ta-da!
500 yen!
I have a lot of 500 yen! I have quite a bit of 500 yen.
Considering it's from my junior high school days, it's quite a bit.
I've got a lot of money in my pocket.
This is my own wallet, by the way.
I'm going to use it today.
I'm going to use it today to have fun at Butashiya.
I'm going.
The weather is so nice!
It's November.
It's 25 degrees today.
I heard it's today.
It's too warm.
It's too hot to wear outerwear.
And you know that knit I'm wearing here?
I've been wearing it about three times a week lately.
I used to buy this when I was in elementary school.
Squid?
I used to buy squid for 60 yen.
That dry kind.
But personally
I liked the chocolate ones.
Dora Chocolate?
You know...
It's like a little dorayaki
with chocolate inside.
That was my favorite.
I haven't been to a dashi shop since I was a freshman in high school.
I haven't been to a dagashiya since I was a freshman in high school.
I'm 22 now.
I used to go to Gashiya. I used to go to a hairbrush shop.
There was an uncle and a grandmother.
I thought the old man was a bit...
I thought he was a little scary.
I mean, he was an uncle.
But when I went there, he was not like that at all.
Sometimes he was quite kind to me.
I feel like I'm moeing through the gap.
Oh, is this the place?
Kobayashi Takahashi Shoten
This is Kobayashi Takahashi Shoten!
It's a holiday today.
I know there are kids here, but there's a lot of people here!
It's a holiday today, so there are children here.
I think I'll go in.
Let's go!
I'm so excited!
Yes, there are a lot of children here!
Let's go in!
There are so many!
I've got 500 yen in my pocket.
Wow, I've never seen this before, but I think there might be a lot!
Oh, my favorite!
Chocobat!
I love chocolate bats!
Here.
This one.
Oh, there are so many things, I don't know where to start!
Oh, all kinds of nostalgia!
It's only 500 yen!It's 500 yen...
I've never seen milk bread before.
45 yen!
What should I do?
Let's go around a bit.
Oh, here it is!
That's the squid I was eating.
Not the sweet kind.
Not this one that tastes sweet.
Not the one that tastes sweet.
I used to eat a lot of salty, snacky squid.
Oh, I love this one, too.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I'll start with this.
Jaga Shio Butter
45 yen!
That's still 45 yen!
But there are 4 pieces in the package, so each piece costs
about 10 yen
There's also a Super Bowl
Eh, wait.
I want this.
Process compact
This is a lottery!
I want to play the lottery!
110 yen
what should I do?
I want to play this!
Huh!Ha!
I miss it.
Have you ever had it?
All these people.
Wow.
They look like they're having fun.
A game of rock, paper, scissors?
So cute!
Sujimaru-kun?
Suisimaru-kun?
Looks good with the pompoms in it.
It's cute.
My friend has a new one.
I'll get one.
Yay!
15 yen for one.
Two for 25 yen.
I'll buy two.
Yay!
Chuchu gummy
I'll buy it!
You used to buy these too.
Why?
Too many gummies?
I love this kind.
Cakes like this.
I haven't done the math, but I'm sure it'll be fine.
I'm hungry.
Maybe I'll buy Kumi, the centerpiece of this album, some snacks.
I wonder what she likes.I wonder what Kumi likes.
This is a petit fortune-telling chocolate.
Oh, Kumi loves Gabricchu! Colorful Gabricchu for Kumi!
I've never seen them before. They're so cute!
I'll get this one, too. I wonder if we'll have enough.
I wonder if we'll have enough. I haven't even counted them out yet.
I think I'll just pay once.
I wonder if it's enough.
I'm getting a little nervous.
Thank you for your help.
I think I'm in a bit of trouble.
Wait a minute, it's not enough.
It's not enough! It's not enough!
Not enough, not enough...
Not enough, not enough, not enough.
There's a lot of games out there. I want to play "Serve Attack," because I used to be a valet.
You just have to make sure it doesn't go down.
What? Why? No ramp.
I'll take a hit. Not the jackpot, but...
I'll take this one.
I've hit it. Here we go.
Home run!
I really want to do this.
If I say this, can we do it now?
Excuse me...
Can you do this lottery?
Yes, I can.Yes, sir.
Yes
Eighty yen.
The one that's turned inside out.
Number 29.
Three
Beauty and Cute
Fun beads set
Not great.
I got this for 100 yen.
I want to make it.
I've already played the game.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
I was able to buy many items.
So I'm going to eat them.
I want to eat them.
Thank you very much.
I found a nice shady spot.
Now let's eat the snacks we bought.
I'll start with the gummies.
I see... so this is how you eat them?
Strawberries?
Strawberries? Yum! Let's try the noodles.
But you'll be right... in my experience.
No.
Nope.hmm
Hmm. Open.
But I went to elementary school every day.
I used to go to the sink shop and eat a home run bar every day.
I used to eat these so much.
I love the toothpick.
Cherry flavor.
Luxury food!
Bon appétit!
Nostalgic taste
What is this?
Candy?
Tastes like candy.
It sticks to your teeth.
Wow, it's great!
Bon appétit.
Yum.
Delicious!
When we rehearse for our shows, the staff always brings snacks and candies.
Sometimes these are included!
But they are very popular, so they run out quickly!
The bill was 450 yen.
But I played too many games, and to be honest, I only had 290 yen.
I'm a little short.
So I borrowed it from the manager.
But if you say it's a snack that costs less than 500 yen...
it's perfect.
So please forgive me.
It's a good plan, isn't it? It's a good plan, isn't it?
I want to do that broadcast you just did.
I've done this before, but I don't think it's ever worked.
Can you put it on like this?
Wouldn't that be great?
Yes!
I didn't think you had it in you.
That's great.
What, like this?
Isn't it great?
Ta-da!
I'll have some panda cotton candy.
Yes, sir.
Delicious.
Why did I buy this?
Bamboo shells.
Pandas are cute
I've always said I like pandas.
but lately I haven't shown that I like pandas much.
I've been saying I like pandas.
I say I like pandas.
I haven't been to the zoo or anything.
This is the last one. Sad.
Wow, you open it like this?
Choco for sponge cake. 40 yen.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
This is amazing!
This is going to fill me up!
Just a little snack. Just a little snack.
What a great idea!
I want to take a nap here.
Sink shop
I really want to go there privately!
Yum!
Thank you for the food!
I've always been cycling and climbing Mt. Takao.
So it was really relaxing.
I thought it was a nice experience.
I enjoyed the candy shop.
I wish there was one near my house.
I'd like to find one and become a candy master.
I've been too lazy to eat at the candy shop this time, so I'd like to do something more active next time.
Next time, I'd like to do something more active.
I don't want to do something scary, so I'd like to do something active again.
I don't want to do something scary, so I want to walk 100 kilometers.
I want to do something active.
So, please subscribe to our channel with the "Good" button.
You don't have to press the button if you don't want to.
You don't have to, but it would be nice if you did.
See you soon.